{
    "id": "c22fa6bd32cf4c0182f6f89545f247ff",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She sings well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Sings is an adverb",
                "Well is an adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d0479d509c8c4c92ab68a3b82ffb8e4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The coffee is very hot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The is an adverb",
                "Very is an adverb",
                "Hot is an adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cbef02b0c17c45909601935119033a20"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kiran is an extremely good dancer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Extremely is an adverb",
                "Good is an adverb",
                "Dancer is an adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07353bd4f1df4c1ab564f183fcfef62d"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is too hot today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Too is an adverb",
                "Today is an adverb",
                "Both of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "39eecd5231e54dd6a95b7cc9e8bcd76c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks all foreign languages fluently.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Speaks is an adverb",
                "All is an adverb",
                "Fluently is an adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "12b6eb10c6b54695bad2cd014af1bf4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child is now happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Child is an adverb",
                "Now is an adverb",
                "Happy is an adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "38ffe61e3a414fa295d84e0de7ffafc9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He learns his lessons very carefully.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Learns is a verb",
                "His is an adverb",
                "Very is an adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "277a7967e8194b8b83652cfcf762c279"
        },
        {
            "question": "I visit my friend daily.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Visit is an adverb",
                "My friend is an adverb",
                "Daily is an adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f0f46039023e4d9784b9afd8509f90ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will return immediately.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will is an adverb",
                "Return is an adverb",
                "Immediately is an adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "12384cac4ba647709444bbe73a16254a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hardly recognized my old friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hardly is an adverb",
                "My is an adverb",
                "Old is an adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7df003659a5540b9a1c38f82847e3bab"
        }
    ]
}